[{"answer": "You know, usually when they lie, they sort of hedge it and they dissemble and they find an element that maybe you can quibble over, you know, what that word really meant or what it didn't mean, but he flat-out lied.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Have you ever seen anything quite like this?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "He thinks probably he can survive this, if he comes, you know, opens up about it and goes into some sort of therapy, says he's going to have some therapy.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Why hasn't he resigned?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "I don't know if he knows or if he doesn't.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "He doesn't know, does he?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "It might be.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "That would become a criminal matter?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "And, you know, he was on a path to becoming the next mayor of New York City if he would have played his cards right.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "And flying ever high, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Probably.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "I mean, is that dream over for him now?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "It's one of these situations where you're caught so blatantly lying.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "Will the lying be more problematic than the original crime?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "Well, watching that clip of you and him, he was so credible, really.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Can anybody believe you again?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Well, I was in the Roosevelt Room when Bill Clinton was accused of the Monica Lewinsky.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "In all your time, Wolf, at CNN, have you ever had anyone in political life, with reasonably high office, look you in the eye and lie like Anthony Weiner did?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "In all my years, and most always, you know, there are plenty of liars out there, but they tell the truth, and if they're going to -- they don't blatantly lie as Anthony Weiner did, so specifically.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Are you the barometer for them lying?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "I think to most Americans, it is.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Do you actually believe that it is material to a man's fitness to preside in high office in American politics as to how he conducts himself in his private life?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Are you a betting man?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "If you were, how long would you give him?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Have you ever drunk alcohol?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "You don't -- you've never taken drugs?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Of course not.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "And presumably, we never -- you never had an affair, because you couldn't have done it?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "And you can say that with total non-Schwarzenegger certainty?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "It better not.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "So this is a -- I would say this is one of your trump cards, because when you look at all these politicians at the moment, whether it's Anthony Weiner or it's John Edwards or it's Arnold Schwarzenegger, the one thing we don't have to worry about in America if you're elected president is anything tumbling out of the -- the cupboard, right, Ann?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "Probably eight.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Michael Sitrick, on a scale of one to 10, just how tarnished is Anthony Weiner's reputation right now?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "I think it is.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Is it retrievable?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "And one of them was Anthony Weiner, right?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "So, he sits down.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "What does he say to you?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "And he opened the conversation with a lie, at which point I replied, I'm Vicky from England, because, you know, if he wants to play chess, I'll play chess, too.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Let's make one thing clear, he was single at the time, but did lie to you about what his occupation was?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "You know, I think what it does is it provides a forum, a platform, if you like, for people's ability or, you know, voluntary sort of deep insecurities.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "How would you describe this new era of Facebook/Twitter infidelity?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "That's a real tough one.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Because he says he didn't have any physical contact with these women?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "You know, I think they're morally both pretty --", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "What's your answer?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "No, because in his mind, he was.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "But is it easy to stand by your mind if in your head and heart you know he wasn't physically unfaithful?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "The same thing to you.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "And what is he doing?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Look, I think that -- I think that Weiner felt that he wasn't cheating, that this was -- you know, look, one of the problems with e-mail is people say things in e-mail, thinking that they're not going to be discovered.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "From a male point of view, what would you say?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "I have not -- you know, I'm going to try to handle this and I haven't ruled out perhaps seeing someone, but I'm not blaming anyone.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Would you seek professional help?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Well, this is the question everyone shakes their head and ask, when they look at young men of any age behaving such as this.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "Why would he do that?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Well, it's interesting that men and women tend to experience this somewhat differently.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "Is it as serious, do you think, as physical infidelity?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "Well, I stopped wearing my suit to be at night.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Is this a deliberate strategy?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "No, not really.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "You have a whole team of people that analyze and debate whether you should wear a tie or not, don't you?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "This is politics, you know?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Well, they're all serious contenders.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Who of all these names do you see as a serious contender at this stage?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "I have --", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "Is there a smoldering volcano?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "I have Romney genes.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "-- that we don't know about?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "I mean, do you honestly believe that a Republican president would have got America out of that hole any faster?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not going to speak about all Republicans.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "-- how is it that America under eight years of the Republicans got themselves into the biggest hole of all time?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Well, a number -- look, a number of the things President Bush did were absolutely right.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "So you would actively distance yourself from the whole Bush years?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Well, I think the president is hoping that we'll be diverted from the fact that ObamaCare is going to get repealed.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "This is, it seems to me, your Achilles' heel, the one where you're in most trouble, because when the president, who is a Democrat, starts praising you for your health care plan, that's not good, is it?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "OMNEY: Let's come -- let's come back.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "But isn't the idea the same?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "You know, the -- if you say the idea is the same, you've got a 2,700 page bill.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "Isn't the idea the same?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Well, the great news is that when I finally debate President Obama, it will be wonderful, because he won't be able to say I'm some heartless Republican that doesn't care about people.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "-- they've got to support?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "-- I -- I point out that there are a number of things in the bill I didn't like, the parts I vetoed.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "Do you have any?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "But let me tell you this, which is I know that a lot of people who say my political prospects would be much, much better if I were just to say oh, it was just a mistake, it was a bone-headed idea, I'm so sorry.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Do you regret it in the way it played out?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "You know, that's really up to the people of Massachusetts.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Has it worked in Massachusetts?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Well, it's up to the people of Massachusetts.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Yes, but has it worked?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "The answer is yes.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Has it worked?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Well, it's about -- I understand it's about one percent of the state budget.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Has it cost more money each year to implement RomneyCare?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "You said a couple of things there.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "But in terms of the ideology, are Republicans who say that it's wrong to take those who can't afford the insurance, to mandate them into getting some form of insurance, are they wrong?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "Nice try.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Let me ask you then, do you personally think homosexuality is a sin?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "I'm going to tell you that as a leader of the American people, I will do everything in my power to treat all people with respect and dignity, and to -- and to advance the rights people have to choose their own course in life.", "docId": "110606pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "Nice try on what?", "qSentId": 614}]